Jonathan Lee

Senior Blockchain / Full Stack Developer

CONTACT

-Phone: +13234127325

-Address: 135 Lake Jogassee Dr Summerville SC 29485

-Git: https://github.com/webdev1109-Mail: jonathantodev421@gmail.com-Skype: live:.cid.75f1231c1e69f305

SUMMARY

Welcome to my resume!

I am a senior blockchain / full-stack developer who has 12+ years of experience. Until now, I completed 20+ big projects and I delivered clients only satisfactory results. I graduated from Osaka University in Japan, and while I was in university, I loved computer programming because I had unusual hobby in computer engineering. So, I studied computer program languages and algorithms very hard and I showed to people my talents.

After graduating from university, I came to United States and I joined Blue Eye soft Corp company with my skills.

There, I had PHP and JavaScript projects first, working as a junior full-stack developer and I completed the projects perfectly within a short time.

After 1 year, I became a senior full-stack developer and from then I developed frontend and backend of big projects.

After that, I joined several companies and I built many websites and web apps using such as JavaScript, React, Vue, Node.js, Express, PHP, Laravel, Python, Django, Flask. Of course, I mastered almost JavaScript and PHP frameworks but my strongest skills are React, Vue, Node, Express, Laravel, Django.

3 years ago, I was very interested in Blockchain so I studied Smart Contract, Solidity, NFT, Solana, Rust very carefully.

At first, Blockchain was a bit difficult to understand because Blockchain is including a lot of new concepts and knowledge.

But I understood web3 soon with a lot of practice and after 1 year, I started to develop main projects using solidity and Rust.

For 2 years, I completed many projects, such as creating of NFT, NFT marketplace, NFT game projects, Solana NFT, etc.

So, now I have rich experience in Blockchain and I can provide great quality to you. My services are following.

- Δ Minimize of gas fee for contract.
- ∆ pixel perfect for frontend
- Δ smart and clean coding.
- Δ optimization of speed.

I will update the project's progress on Github daily and I can work 8+hours every day according to your requirements.

Only perfect result!!!

Thanks for visiting resume.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Software Development.

Osaka University,

1-1 Yamadaoka, Suita, Osaka 565-0871, Japan,

2009 - 2013.

Relevant Coursework: Operating Systems Architecture, Linux/Unix Programming, Usability in Website and Software Design, C++ Programming I & II, Web Page Development, Relational Database Design & SQL, Data Engineering, Advanced Software Programming.

SKILLS

Main Skills:

Blockchain: Smart Contract, NFT, Solidity, Web3, Uniswap, Rust, Solana

Frontend: React, Redux, Vue, Angular, Next, Nuxt

Backend: Node, Express, Nest, Django, Laravel

- Creating NFT (including Solana NFT), Building Contracts, Building Frontend using Web3, React, Vue, Next
- Building NFT marketplace, Minting tokens according to user's requirements
- Building NFT game (3d game using Unity and Three.js as frontend, Node.js as backend, Smart contract as blockchain, WebSocket)
- Backend development, using Node, Express, Koa.js, Laravel, Django, Flask, ASP.NET Core / MVC, GraphQL
- Frontend development, using JavaScript / TypeScript, React / React Hooks / Saga / Redux, Vue / Vuex, Angular
- Design and development of big database, using PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, DynamoDB, Oracle
- React Native for building Mobile app.
- UI Framework, including Bootstrap, Telerik Kendo UI, Ant Design, Material UI / Kit, React Bootstrap, Semantic UI
- CSS, Sass, Less for style

- Git. Git Flow for version control
- Understanding of different types of testing (Unit / Integration / Functional)
- AWS cloud service / Aws lambda / Azure / API gateway, Amplify, Cognito
- REST API
- Next.js, Nuxt.js for Server Side Rendering.
- Fast Static-Site Generation Web Framework Gatsby
- Payment Integration for Paypal and Stripe
- Mail notification using several frameworks
- Testing Automation: Jest, Cypress, Jasmine, Enzyme, Mocha, Chai, Ava, Karma, Protractor, Agouti
- Three.js and WebGL.
- WebSocket, socket.io, bubble.io

WORK EXPERIENCE

Blockchain Developer.

SPOKES DIGITAL(Remote), August 2019 – December 2020

- Implemented NFT marketplace using Smart Contract, Solidity, React.js, Web3.js.
- Implemented vesting and claiming NFT contracts.
- Implemented new blockchain technologies and completed professional market research.
- Built and launched Smart Contracts for Genesis NFT, Pode and Marketplace as well using ERC-721 rather than ERC-1155.
- Built Stacking Rewards contract, so investors earn MONA tokens by stacking NFTs and LP tokens.
- Built multi-cryptocurrency wallet with embedded exchange.
- Contributed to DeFi platform frontend MVP using React and Web3.js.
- Developed cryptocurrency staking system backend and dashboard MVP.
- Built real-time 3D WebGL game using Solidity, NFT, React, Three.js.
- Contributed to various blockchain projects Enigma, Kava, constellation network.
- Built multithreaded integration test system for Quiver blockchain.
- Built Smart Contract for CVR token as a Blockchain developer.
- Worked on building desktop wallet using QML.
- Built DApps, software consisting of frontend and decentralized backend.

Senior Full Stack Developer.

Krumware, May 2018 – June 2019

- Implemented pixel perfect frontend by design of client.
- 3d animation effect websites using Three.js and WebGL.

- Built websites using React & Django.
- Implemented SEO (Search Engine Optimization) to existing websites.
- Retrieved data from multiple, different storage APIs, using GraphQL.
- Payment Integration.
- Implemented Mail notification on several frameworks including React, Laravel, etc.
- Implemented Chat bot integration to several websites.
- Built big webslites using React as frontend and Laravel as Backend and MongoDB, MySQL as Database.
- Completed Online game using Unity and Node.js and Websocket.
- Made online game (Poker) using Phaser3 and Node.js and Socket.io.
- Built United States website using Laravel Livewire and Vue.js.
- Web Hosting to AWS / CloudWays / Cpanel.

Senior Full Stack Developer.

CENTRILOGIC (Remote), July 2016 – April 2018

- Built Websites using React, Redux, Django, DynamoDB.
- Used ASP.NET Core and Python Flask and Java.
- Developed an internal application that tracked the life of an order through a windows service and MongoDB.
- Improved SQL Server performance with stored procedure refactors and new constraints and indexes.
- Used GraphQL and REST API
- Development of Electron App and Used Next.js and Nuxt.js
- Web Hosting to AWS / Azure.

Junior Full Stack Developer.

Blue Eye Soft Corp, June 2013 – May 2015

- Implemented Single Page Application (SPA) architecture and client side MVC using AngularJS.
- Used Bootstrap features such as Model objects, Tabs, Tooltips, Carousals throughout the application.
- Used Angular UI Grid directives such as filters, rootscope, childscope, modal, and template etc.
- Implemented components and wire-frames using cross-browser compatible CSS, JavaScript, jQuery and AJAX, Angular JS.
- Used ng-view directive to refresh only certain section of the page and reduce the load on the web server.
- Developed automated software which manages infrastructure without human intervention.
- Built multiple language website using Laravel with Vue.js frontend developer.

- Built shopping website using Django with React.js frontend developer.
- Implemented SEO(Search Engine Optimization) for several websites.
- Paypal integration using Laravel and Node.js.
- Web Scraping using Python.
- Web Hosting to Azure / CWP.

TYPICAL PROJECTS

∆ **Leapn** (https://leapn.life)

2021

My client Swaraj wanted me to build an NFT game and game site to mint tokens.

They are building amazing 3d games and token will use on their game.

I built a gaming site using Next.js and I built NFT tokens and contracts to connect the website using ERC-721, Web3.js, Solidity.

I deploy contracts to test net so they checked contracts and gas fees in detail. And then I deployed contracts to the Ethereum main net and website to AWS.

- NFT / Solidity / Web3.js
- Next.is
- Amazon Web Service.

Now, all tokens are minted and they deploy tokens to opensea.io.

They will launch the game soon and they will make more profit from that tokens.

△ **AlturaNFT** (https://app.alturanft.com)

2021

My client Neil wanted me to build an NFT marketplace using smart contracts, web3.js, React.js, Node.js, Express.js.

He already had NFT tokens and he only wanted to sell that token in the marketplace. I built the frontend using React.js from his design, and I built the backend to save some data using Node.js, Express.js.

And I connected the frontend and contracts using web3.js.

- Smart Contracts / NFT / Web3.js / Solidity
- React.js
- Node.js / Express.js
- MongoDB

They already sold a lot of tokens and most people are interested in that marketplace. so, I think, they will sell all tokens and they will make more profit via marketplace.

△ **DizzyDragons** (https://dizzydragons.club)

2021

I built NFTs using solidity and I deployed them to Ethereum main network. My client George wanted to me manage full project so I built frontend and contracts. Frontend is based on React.js and of course I used web3.js to connect frontend and contracts.

- NFT / ERC-721 / Solidity / Web3.js
- React.js

- Amazon web service

He launched NFTs in time and Users can mint NFTs on that website. Now, 1400 tokens of them are minted so he made profit from them. Of course, he will make more profit by minting, staking, etc.

△ **Webaverse** (https://app.webaverse.com)

2020

(https://github.com/webdev1109/threejsgameapp-webaverse)

My client Michale wanted me to join his team.

At that time, his team members are building a 3D game using Three.js, React.js, Vite.js, Node.js, MongoDB, Smart Contracts.

I built a game landing page game logic using React.js and Vite.js, Three.js. He already hired a solidity developer so I worked on the only frontend, but I had to connect to contracts so I used Web3.js.

He provided me with all models such as .gltf files, .glb files, and I built these parts of game-like camera control and moving objects in the space, etc.

- Three.is
- Smart Contract / Solidity / Web3.js
- React.js / Vite.js
- PostgreSQL / MongoDB
- Node.js

They were able to launch a game in time and a lot of users are visiting that game. so, they connected metamask wallet and they are making more profit from cryptocurrencies.

△ Pottorff (https://www.pottorff.com)

2020

(https://github.com/webdev1109/laravel-vue)

My client Linda wanted to me Build her website from her design using Laravel Livewire and Vue.js.

Pottorff is her company and she is in technical team of company.

They made great louvers and dampers and they wanted to build a website to introduce their products.

So, she was finding a full-stack developer on behalf of the company and she hired me through the test.

This project includes complex Vue.js UI components and Laravel Livewire, axios, jsTree, MySQL database.

I had 3 team members and I built this site with my team.

As a team leader, I managed every part of project and I developed Product pages using jsTree, axios, etc.

Also, I built all admin pages that require powerful security because I am the most excellent developer and leader.

- Vue.js / jsTree / Typescript
- Laravel Livewire
- MvSQL
- Mail notification

- Web Hosting to Cloudways

Her company was able to introduce their business and they were able to keep in touch with many teams or individuals all around the world. So, they could produce a lot of products and get more profit.

∆ **Bitono** (<u>https://bitono.io</u>)

2019

My client Tam wanted me to build his betting site using Vue.js and Laravel with my creative idea from scratch.

The Structure and design were complicated and he wanted pixel perfect.

At first, he wanted me to build frontend so, I built frontend with my creative idea and his design using Vue.js UI components.

After that, he wanted to me implement some parts of Laravel backend and I implemented Paypal integration, stripe integration, Verification by using Email, Real time Notification by using Websocket, Chart API.

- Vue.js / TypeScript
- Laravel
- Websocket
- Chart API
- Payment Integration
- Mail notification
- MySQL / MongoDB
- AWS cloud service

His team manages the betting system and a lot of people are playing the game. They are making more profit from management of game and their business are growing up more and more.

△ **Spreadshirt** (https://www.spreadshirt.com)

2019

My client Rafael wanted me to take part in updating their existing website. It is multiple language website and it included complex UI and several payment

methods.

I built Men and Women pages using MERN(MongoDB, Express, React, Node) stack and PostgreSQL.

The project uses Yarn 2 and follows the zero-install strategy.

Yarn performs a check-sum against the dependencies currently installed.

It is a micro-frontend react application, with a Service Oriented Architecture.

I used Emotion to style react components in JS, using emotions CSS prop with the object styles syntax.

- React / TypeScript
- Websocket
- Atomic Design
- Node.js / Express
- MongoDB / PostgreSQL
- AWS Cloud Service / Lambda function.

The company was able to update the site on time and acquire 100,000+ users. The company was able to manage the business on a global scale and they were able to have many online agencies. So, they can advertise and sell many products on the online stores and they made a lot of profits.

△ Uniclix (https://uniclixapp.com)

2018

My client David wanted our team to build his company's website using Laravel & React.

This Project includes React UI components, Redux, Laravel, Websoket, Chatbot Integration, etc.

At that time, I was Senior React and Laravel developer and the team leader gave me many parts of the project.

I developed Products, Blog, Pricing pages, and I solved technical problems that happen in the backend.

For example, chatbot integration, Laravel - Websocket, Laravel - MongoDB, etc.

- React / Redux
- Laravel
- Websocket
- MySQL / MongoDB
- Chatbot Integration
- Mail notification / SEO
- AWS cloud service

The company was able to launch the service on time and acquire 2000+ users. Client was able to achieve the purpose and they advertised their business successfully via site.

△ **Ovolo** (https://ovologroup.com)

2018

My client Noha wanted me to build a hotel introduction and booking system website using React, Gatsby, Django.

It includes React Material UI, Redux, Mail notification, Payment integration, etc.

The project uses Yarn 2 and follows the zero-install strategy.

Yarn performs a check-sum against the dependencies currently installed.

I built the frontend using React Material UI, Redux, Gatsby from his design, and I combined to backend with axios.

- React / Redux / Gatsby
- Django
- DvnamoDB
- Mail notification
- Payment integration
- AWS cloud service

The company was able to start business on time and acquire 3000+ users. Nowadays, many customers book hotel and pay them via site. so, they are making \$1500000+ profits per year and they are providing blast to many users.

△ **Culturestudio** (https://www.culturestudio.net)

2017

My client Jeker wanted me to build website shopping with other developers using Shopify, Vue.js, Core-js, etc.

This website is an online shop to order and buy the shirts, hats, shoes, etc.

I built the frontend using Vue.js, Core-js, Bootstrap from the client's design.

Also, I built an API system from the API documentation of the backend developer and I got all data using axios.

And I used Vuex to build a simple and structured website and to remove complex errors.

- Vue / Core-js / Vuex
- Bootstrap
- Shopify
- PostgreSQL
- payment Integration
- Web hosting to Cloudways

The company was able to launch the service on time and acquire 4000+ users. They are selling many products including shirts, hats, shoes and they are providing convenience for users via site.

Now, the company is able to generate revenue and they are making plans to expand their business via site.

△ Pcpartpicker (https://pcpartpicker.com)

2017

My client Johnson wanted me to take part in building his company's site using Django, Python, jQuery UI, etc.

They are building electronic circuits, and they wanted customers to build products and test the product using their sites.

He wanted me to build list pages and propose an algorithm to test the products. I used jQuery UI, jQuery, HTML to build the list page and I fetched all data using Python. And I made an Algorithm test the circuit and I calculated the total wattage from every device's wattage using the calculating wattage algorithm.

- HTML / CSS
- JavaScript / TypeScript
- Django / Python
- Algorithm
- Websocket

The company was able to launch the site on time and users were able to make electronic circuit by themself and check the safety.

Now, a lot of users are using this site and they check the circuit and order perfect products via site.

The company is making more profit as building and selling the products that users order via site.

Language

- English (Fluent, Advanced speaking)
- Japanese (Native)
- Chinese (Middle, Advanced reading and writing)
- Korean (Beginner, Advanced reading)

Certification

1. HackerRank (July 08, 2018)

Mastering React certification, Node.js Certification

2. Coursera (May 13, 2017)

Python Certification, Laravel Certification

Training Courses

1. Udemy (July 08, 2016)

Full Stack React & Redux & Node.js

I learned how to combine React and Redux.

React is a very good JavaScript library but it has some limits.

But they are removed with Redux.

I learned advantages of MERN stack and I mastered how to make perfect project with MERN stack.

2. LinkedIn Learning (June 12, 2018)

Master Laravel with Vue.js Full stack development.

Laravel is top PHP framework and it has powerful security.

Recently, many clients build website using Laravel & Vue.

Through this course, I mastered Laravel and Vue and I had high ability what can build wonderful Laravel & Vue projects.

3. University of Phoenix (September 18, 2019)

Project planning and Implementation

This course provides the foundation for successful project planning, organization, and implementation within the realm of information technology. Topics covered include project scoping, estimating, budgeting, scheduling and staffing, tracking and controlling, and software tools for project management. Through this course, I learned the most important details to design and implement successful projects.